Justin Henry Flores

Justin.H.Flo@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Intermediate with HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Excellent Verbal and Written Javascript, React, and Node.js
- Intermediate with Python, Django, Java, Proficient with Zoom, Agile, Jira, and Spring Boot, PHP, MySQL, Git, and JSON
- Novice with JQuery and XML
- Clear Understanding of REST API, DevOps, Analysis and A/B Testing Docker, Kubernetes, and Relational **Database Concepts**
- Advanced Analytical and Problem Solving Skills
- Efficient and Good Time Management

- Communication
- Scrum
- Clear Understanding of Regression
- Fast Learner
- Self Starter

WEBSITE

https://justin-h-flo.github.io/Website

CERTIFICATES

IBM Full Stack Software Developer

https://coursera.org/share/b9de1c4c16106ec9a01f11803e5fd021

Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate

https://www.credly.com/badges/d4ef2634-36b5-43f8-af4a-9ad12ca41118/public_url

Python for Everybody

https://coursera.org/share/11ec97dfe5bbf130b0beaaf64db468cd

Java as a Second Language

https://coursera.org/share/e88132a91ae3ce6028294c5c1fc8494f

Agile with Atlassian Jira

https://coursera.org/share/23efccae58f1fe756ae48cb82bc619c3

Wharton's Business Analytics Specialization

https://coursera.org/share/7bc912b714cd889f366ccce81c6f3a20

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

My MacREU research internship was a paid summer internship that was funded by a National Science Foundation (NSF) award. I had the opportunity to work full time for 10 weeks on a research project. All of the students had the chance to do team building

exercises which allowed us to develop our interpersonal skills. I also had the chance to present my work at the North American Solid State Chemistry Conference.

EDUCATION

University of California, Riverside - Riverside, CA | Bachelor of ArtsNeuroscience

WORK HISTORY

DELIVERY DRIVER | 06/2020 to Current **Doordash**

- Communicated customer complaints, requests and feedback to company management for swift resolution.
- Fostered positive working relationships with regular customers.
- Completed rush deliveries on tight timetables to satisfy customer needs.

RESEARCHER | 10/2021 to 05/2022

University Of California, Riverside - Riverside, CA

- Collaborated with colleagues on a scientific publication.
- Conducted research into topics to provide valuable contributions.
- Interpreted and analyzed research data to draw conclusions on outcomes.
- Presented complex scientific topics in an understandable manner.

RESEARCH ASSISTANT | 07/2018 to 03/2020

University Of California, Riverside - Riverside, CA

- Proficient with working in a glove box with a nitrogen atmosphere while performing exceptional synthetic work with chemicals. As well as sealing quartz tubes with a torch.
- Collaborated with colleagues on a scientific publication.
- Analyzed powder and single crystal X-ray diffraction data.

PUBLICATIONS

Ortner, T. S., Scheifers, J. P., Flores, J., Zhang, Y., Iyer, A. K., Gesing, T. M., & Fokwa, B. P. (2019). An old dog with new tricks – additions to the cesium lithium chloride system: Cs3Li2Cl5 and the hydrated Cs3LiCl4·4H2O. European Journal of Inorganic Chemistry, 2019(30), 3526–3535. https://doi.org/10.1002/ejic.201900774

Scheifers, J. P., Flores, J. H., Janka, O., Pöttgen, R., & Fokwa, B. P. (2022). Triangular arrangement of ferromagnetic iron chains in the high-Tc ferromagnet TiFe1-xOs2+xB2. Chemistry – A European Journal, 28(42). https://doi.org/10.1002/chem.202201058